Hossein Sadeghi

Mashhad, Khorasan, Iran



sadeghihossein.hs@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/hossein-sadeghi-077092209

Summary

Experienced Frontend Web Developer with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry. Skilled in Communication Training, English, Angular, Python, JavaScript, HTML, Teamwork, and SCSS. Strong engineering professional with a Bachelor's degree focused in Computer Engineering from Sadjad University of Technology.

Experience



Chief Technology Officer - Frontend Web Developer

Saminrayaneh

Sep 2021 - Present (1 year 1 month +)

Teaching Assistant

Sadjad University of Technology

Oct 2019 - Aug 2022 (2 years 11 months)

Teaching Assistant in Advance C++ Programming

Frontend Web Developer

Saminrayaneh

Nov 2020 - Sep 2021 (11 months)

Senior Frontend Developer with Angular

Frontend Web Developer

HRCanDo

Jan 2021 - May 2021 (5 months)

Frontend Angular Developer - Contract

Chief Technology Officer - Full Stack Developer

Ratagostar

Mar 2020 - Nov 2020 (9 months)

Full Stack Developer

Ratagostar

Jan 2019 - Mar 2020 (1 year 3 months)

Full-Stack Developer

Frontend Developer with Angular

Backend Developer With NestJs

Frontend Web Developer Intern

Ratagostar Oct 2018 - Jan 2019 (4 months)

Education

★ Sadjad University of Technology

Bachelor's degree, Computer Engineering Sep 2018 - Jul 2022

Imam Reza High School (Mashhad)

High School Diploma, Mathematics Sep 2014 - Sep 2018

Licenses & Certifications

C++ - Sololearn 1051-17544430

S Python For Data Science - Sololearn

17544430-1161

S Python Core - Sololearn 1073-17544430

Full Python Course (Basics, Image Processing, pygame, Machine Learning, Deep Learning, Data Analytics) - Sajjad Aemmi

Skills

Angular • python • C++ • Full-Stack Development • Pygame • PostgreSQL • Data Analytics • Representational State Transfer (REST) • Back-End Web Development • Artificial Intelligence (AI)